[{"answer": "I was because you weren't doing her any favors by condescendingly trying to convince her that she's a victim.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'll tell you why I said that, Piers.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Why would you say that?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "-- to black people.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Do you think she's stupid, Larry?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Racism is not a major problem in America anymore, Piers.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Do you think she's stupid, Larry?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I think that I would rather have a George Zimmerman living in my neighborhood and maybe if George Zimmerman was living my neighborhood we'd have a few fewer Ariel Castros.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Do you think that Rachel Jeantel is stupid?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "You treated George Zimmerman like he's some sort of criminal.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Could you just answer my question?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "It was an unfortunate incident.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Trayvon Martin wasn't committing crimes in that neighborhood, was he?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "I don't speak Ebonics as well as Rachel, if that's what you mean.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Just out of interest, how many languages do you speak?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "You don't think she's a smart cookie.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "And the relevance of that is what?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I know how she presented herself on the jury.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Do you know her educational background, Larry?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "People evaluate you the way -- based on the way you express yourself.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Larry, do you know her educational background or not?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Why don't you hire her if she's so sharp as a co-host, Piers?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "I know she came across on the jury.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Yes or no?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Because actually I think it's relevant.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Why are we even talking about this?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Larry.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Where are the cameras?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Her grades -- her grades has since slipped to two something because of the stress that she suffered understandably from the death of her friend Trayvon.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Did she sound to you like somebody you want to hire in any kid of (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "No, I think the facts in the case are clear.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Did she fired the shot to try and kill him?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well, that's kind of a difficult question.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Did she actually claim Stand Your Ground as a defense or self-defense?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "And in the trial it was self-defense because you'd already failed in the attempt to have Stand Your Ground as a defense?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Well, we know that there is tremendous disparity based on race in the entire criminal justice system, rates of arrests, rates of indictment, rates of conviction, rates of appellate reversal, rates of commutation, rates of release on parole.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, I mean, on the face of it, this is a total fast, isn't it?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Because that's -- that's been on television and that's in the mind of many people in Florida.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "What I was confused by there and if you can actually clear this up, but why would she refer to Stand Your Ground, given that that was not the defense that was actually put up?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Well, not only that.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "It would seem an absolutely perfect example of what that law is intended for?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "It's intense.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What is it like in that room when you're deliberating when perhaps you don't all agree to start with about what the verdict should be?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I voted for the death penalty.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "How did you vote in that?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Yes, there was definitely an element of frustration.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "And were you frustrated that more of your colleagues didn't?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "LLEN-COOGAN: In my opinion, the verdict ended up -- this is really difficult because I wasn't there.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "You weren't following it as closely, obviously, as they were, but from what you've seen and heard about it, what was your view of it?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Well, there are rules that limit testimony to relevance and after all, Trayvon Martin was not on trial.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "That is a failure of the prosecution, isn't it?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Well, definitely the lack of sequestration we would have lost some of our jurors if we had had to have been sequestered.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Do you think that either of those things were beneficial to what you went through compared to Zimmerman jurors or perhaps not so beneficial?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "LUMACKI: I just think \"Rolling Stone\" is a different type of publication.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "What is the difference really between, say, \"The New York Times\" or the \"New York Post,\" putting that same picture on their cover as they did at the time, and \"Rolling Stone\" choosing to do it now with a much longer lead in with these kind of issues?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, and I actually don't think that \"Rolling Stone\" is entirely on the other side of the spectrum.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "What is the difference between \"TIME\" magazine doing it when they do celebrities and serious issues and \"Rolling Stones\" do?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I've read most of it.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "You read the piece, right?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Well, it's a good debate to have and I'm not a fan at all of the Stand Your Ground laws.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "What do you think of the whole Stand Your Ground debate that's raging now?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "Look, I think -- I've heard your segments with Alan Dershowitz, who -- old friend and colleague.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Would you have prosecuted Zimmerman under second-degree murder or manslaughter or not at all?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Well, I would have preferred not to have needed to be a comeback kid, but that's --", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "Do you like being the comeback kid?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Have they been policed properly in your view since the huge crash?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "Well, look, I don't read too much into polls.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "What does that tell you about the American public's power of forgiveness?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "Look, I'll say only this.", "docId": "130717pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "Do you want to clarify that?", "qSentId": 720}]